<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-10-18T17:49:21+00:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Bisanz Lab Website</title><subtitle>Website of the Bisanz Lab interested in the gut microbiome, drugs, toxins, and diet.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Help wanted!</title><link href="/2023/10/04/TechJob.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Help wanted!" /><published>2023-10-04T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2023-10-04T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/2023/10/04/TechJob</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/10/04/TechJob.html"><![CDATA[<p>We are currently seeking a lab technician. Please click to find out more.</p>

<p><strong>Job Description:</strong>
The Bisanz lab in the Department of Biochemistry and Molecular Biology, and One Health Microbiome Center at The Pennsylvania State University (University Park, PA) is searching for a full-time Research Technologist 1. The candidate will join a growing and dynamic team dedicated to understanding how the microbes of the human body (the microbiome) impact health and disease.</p>

<p>The candidate’s responsibilities will include research activities, maintenance of cutting-edge equipment, supervision of lower level staff and/or students, and administrative tasks including inventory management and purchasing. This position is well suited to recent graduates interested in a career in biotechnology and/or attending graduate school; however, all qualified individuals are encouraged to apply.</p>

<p><strong>Education and Experience:</strong>
This position typically requires a Bachelor’s degree or higher plus 1 year of related experience or an equivalent combination of education and experience. The candidate will have a minimum of a Bachelor of Science in a relevant field of the life sciences, or equivalent experience. Applicants must demonstrate that they are detail oriented, highly self-motivated, organized, and be enthusiastic to work both individually and as part of a collaborative and multidisciplinary team. The applicant must have non-course based lab experience and/or previous experience working in a laboratory technician role.</p>

<p><strong>Additional Information:</strong>
Applications must be submitted electronically and include a resume or CV, contact information for 2-3 references, and a cover letter detailing your relevant experiences and how you will contribute to building an inclusive lab culture.
<br />
To apply please visit <a href="https://psu.wd1.myworkdayjobs.com/PSU_Staff/job/Penn-State-University-Park/Job-Posting-Title-Research-Technologist-1_REQ_0000049150-1">here</a>.</p>]]></content><author><name>jordan-bisanz</name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are currently seeking a lab technician. Please click to find out more.]]></summary></entry></feed>